Thank you for watching
Nogisaka Audio
Dance
Today's show is the Nogisaka Codition!
I'm Bananamo, the host of the show, and I'm looking forward to working with you.
And here are our guests.
What's going on?
Give me my prize!
Why did you think it was an afterthought?
What⁉reward? A reward?
Mr. Kimura, please announce today's project.
I'll do my best if I have this! Reward briefing!
Nogizaka Honji-jin, I've been getting the impression that you've been doing a lot of punishment games lately.
No, it's not just this show that has so many penalty games.
I'm so jealous!
Lately, in the prime time shows, they don't have games with a lot of punishment.
There aren't any, are there?
There aren't any.
Why is it different here?
It's because of the time of day, and because the management allows us to do whatever we want.
It's also because the management allows it.
It would be cute and interesting if everyone did it.
That's right.
We've put too much effort into the penalty game, and we've reflected on that.
This time, we're going to present a prize that everyone would like to receive.
I'll ask them to present how much they want it.
We'll use this as a reference for future programming.
First of all, I'd like to introduce three rewards that Yoda would like to receive.
Small Reward
Here they are!
Massage dog
What kind of massage dog is a massage dog?
I've been a bit out of shape lately.
During the school year, one of the students would come up behind me and rub me like this.
He rubs me like this.
That's how big the show got.
I bought a massage chair for the show.
But I couldn't bring it there, so... But as I said, I can't take that there.
So it would be weirder to have a masseuse there, too.
Here Yoda will be asked to announce what he can do for the massage dog
Anything you two want me to say... out loud, like a speaker.
I see... the kind of words you want them to say.
Anything.
It's okay to have them say "something" or "anything.
That's a good idea.
This is the show.
Next, Yoda's prize is a round-the-world trip.
A trip around the world.
Secondhand?
I was expecting something like this in college.
You don't get stuff like this in college.
What would you do if you got a round-the-world trip?
That's a lot.
I'll only do one thing.
Anything?
That's a pretty wide range.
I mean, not just dying.
Sure.
But if it's not about the office or dying, then...
No facial tattoos, right?
Yes, that's true.
What do you think of it from the office's point of view?
From my point of view, it's fine.
No, it's fine.
Don't go around the world with a face tattoo.
And Yoda's best reward...
Playing with Mr. Bananaman.
That makes me so happy.
What's better than a round-the-world trip?
Stop it!
We're more than happy to play with Mr. Bananaman.
What do you mean?
I want to go trampolining.
He listens to everything.
Trampolining and eating together. We did trampoline and had dinner together.
And then we'd play ping-pong and stuff again.
We'd really play for a day.
Just playing.
What about Yoda, who would do anything if he could play with Bananaman?
I can shave my hair.
That's why you don't do punkish stuff like that.
You just want to play.
That's why.
I can pose just fine.
I practice belly dancing.
I can scoop soil.
That's just an extension of having fun all day.
They want us to do belly dancing.
After belly dancing, we'll go trampolining.
I don't know.
Can we do it on location or something?
I want to be on location.
On location.
It doesn't have to be on location.
Why are you trampolining on a track in private?
Then we'll have dinner and discuss it together.
It's true.
Then Kubo announces the reward he wants
A small reward
This way
Potatoes!
What's going on?
I have no idea what it means.
What are you doing with potatoes?
They're harvested in Hokkaido and left to lie in the snow.
They're sweet and sugary.
The kind of potatoes you can't get at the supermarket.
Oh.
You know, that kind of thing.
What will you do with the potatoes?
If you give me potatoes, I'll work as a staff member for a day.
For the show? The program?
Yes, that day.
I'll be helping the crew, not the taping crew.
You'll really have to do it, though, won't you?
I'm serious.
We'll have lots of laughs and ha-ha-ha's.
I'm watching a boring show.
They're laughing at us.
It's called staff laughter.
I'm going to practice doing that.
And what's a better reward than potatoes?
Mananaman and I have the same thing!
You're saying that again, aren't you?
You got the jigsaw puzzle the other day, didn't you?
I was really happy to receive it from the Nimura team
Just the three of us.
What's this? It's like a reward party for us.
Practical lonti.
It's not practical.
It's got all three of our stuff in it.
We'll take a picture of it and make a rontie out of it.
It would be great if we could cut it at a rehearsal or something.
If you can give me that lonti...
There's often a penalty drink, right?
We drink a lot here.
That's not a punishment.
For example, if I'm told to drink, I drink.
I'd say, "That's terrible!
To be honest, I'm not very good at it.
I go in, and I don't even pause for a second.
I never make a sour face.
I don't even make a disgusted face.
Can I ask you a question?
How many shots are you allowed?
Drinks?
I can do three drinks.
Three shots, three shots.
I can drink a whole bunch of Tatas in a row. I'll drink Tata Tata in a row or whatever.
But now, let's take a picture, for example, of the three of us.
If it's at a later date, we can do a lonti or something.
You can do that?
Really?
What do you mean?
You want to do it now?
I'd love to.
Do you have a drink?
Do you have any?
I have some right now.
I'm so happy.
Three bullets.
Oh, man.
Shall we have a drink first?
I'll take a drink first, then we'll take a picture.
Bon appétit.
I didn't like the look on your face.
No, no, no. I'm totally happy.
You said you'd be right in.
No, I'm happy.
Yumiki said so. That's why there are three.
No, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait!
Mr. BERNANAMAN!
Mr. Barnerman.
Because I didn't say anything about three.
Yes, you did.
So I happened to have Propolis 2024
What are you going to do for a reward, Kubo?
Then take a picture after you drink this and we'll make it later
I'm so happy
Can you say "kon-kon-kon"?
Yes, without looking bad
I'd appreciate it.
Bon appétit!
The smell is amazing. Oh, man, that smells great.
Oh, shit.
What?
That's what I'm talking about.
You don't look so bad.
Let's take a picture.
I don't know. It's normal.
Smile.
Awesome propolis news!
Now that's a good picture
Onkke onkke.
You got it!
Next is Yamashita. First of all, he announced his post-award prize
A boiled egg and potato kenpin!
I love them. I can basically live for a day with boiled eggs.
If this is all right with you, but what will you do for me?
If you give it to me, I'll wear tights to the shoot.
That's too much. It's not worth it.
Just one boiled egg. You're the one who wants to wear tights.
I don't want to. I really don't, but I'll do it.
Does it have to be a fancy egg or something?
And for the reward of salted bread and tarts, Yamashita can do...
He'll get his face smashed in!
Yamashita's best reward is...
Here it is!
A box of sea urchins! A box of sea urchins!
It's not often you get a box of sea urchins for a project, so if he gets this, he'll get a face full of sea urchins...
I'm going to paint my face.
I'm going to whitewash your face.
I think it's the most humiliating thing an idol can do.
It's just a dirty look.
I can go buy it right away!
What do you have that you can go buy right away?
Can you open the door, Mr. Himura?
Open!
Bagun from Hokkaido.
Painted white? Paint it white?
Paint it white and you'll get it! Paint it white and you'll get it!Paint it white and you'll get it! Paint it white and you'll get it!
It's so beautiful. It's from the market.
Paint it white? Whitewash. It'll stay on.
Maybe you shouldn't do that, but I don't understand why you have to look like that.
You've been in so many dramas, and here you are, in whiteface.
It'll only ruin your career.
You definitely shouldn't do that. I'm going.
You're going? What's with her?
I just happened to get lucky.
So, while we wait for Yamashita's whitewash, we'll go to Inoue's presentation.
Oh, I'm sorry. Delicious strawberries.
If I could have some strawberries...
Strawberries are good.
Yes, they are.
What do you think of strawberries?
Strawberry is good.
Strawberries are good.
You just barely made it.
When we did the birthday show...
Haruka-san brought us strawberries every day.
Every day?
From your parents.
It was the first time I ate white strawberries.
You ate them for the first time?
I was surprised that they were white inside.
Strawberries are good. White ones.
Strawberries are good.
What would you do if you could have strawberries?
If I could have strawberries.
I'd play the chili chair.
Are you serious?
Why would you do that?
The chatterbox and strawberries.
Have you ever done the chili chair?
No, I haven't.
No, I haven't.I don't have it.
It's pretty scary.
That's scary.
And for blueberries...
Inoue's best reward...
Inoue's best reward was
Delicious tangerines!
Oranges?
Mandarin oranges?
Fruit?
Fruit shower.
The best reward. Just oranges?
If I could have a tasty tangerine.
I'll eat the ghetto.
Hey! Hey!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
But someone already proved that you can eat them.
I personally think it's possible.
I've eaten a lot of them, but it's really tough when you see them in front of you.
Mr. Kimura is under a spell that says he can only eat insects.
I can buy them.
Oranges are easy to buy.
Anda?
Anne.
Oh, mandarin oranges.
Why?
That's great!
So we put some delicious tangerines on top, and stand by for something we also happened to have on hand.
Well, Inoue, let's open it ourselves!
Scary!
That's scary!
Here we go!
Wait!
It's a bug!
What's this?
It's a bamboo worm.
A bamboo worm. Bamboo Bug
Bamboo insect
It's already an insect, isn't it?
It's a bug.
But it's like a tiny potato fry.
Oh no, wait a minute!
The more I think about it, the more it looks like a bug.
Then it's a bug.
It's a bug.
You don't have to eat the whole thing, but I'd like you to eat two or three.
Not just one more.
This is the worst.
It's got a face.
It's long.
But we'll get some tasty oranges.
Here we go.
Can you do it?
Yes, sir.
I'm going.
Oh, my God.
It's got it!
Bon appétit!
I just ate it... you didn't just serve it, you ate it.
It's delicious... but うまの...
Like a potato without the filling.
Shall we try some?
No, no, I won't eat it. I don't even have mandarin oranges.
I don't want just one.
I want you to hold it and chew on it.
And show them how it looks before you eat it.
That's it. Put it down. Put it down, put it down.
Put it down, put it down, put it down.
Oh, my God!
I'm eating a bug, and the world is like...
I wish you'd eat it with a little more salt and pepper, but you can't taste it anymore.
It's so empty. It's true, it's a bit empty.
I'm sorry, I'm in.
I'm in! I'm in! I'm in!
Okay, oranges.
Congratulations!
No, one mandarin orange. That's right.
Now let's taste the tasty mikan we got from the ghetto!
The skin is so thin!
Yes, they're sweet.
Actually, I was just saying how good they are!
He was grabbing at the staff!
And then he said, "I can proudly serve this with oranges.
So you ate it?
I ate some oranges.
That's the worst.
It's not the worst.
I didn't eat any bugs.
Sorry. Yamashita's ready.
Yamashita's here. Yamashita's here.
Okay, okay, okay, okay
Seasoning Yamashita
Yamashita Sensei, Yamashita Sensei
Put it away, put it away
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Here you go, Yamashita. Yamashita-sensei, it's done.
Try not to show it to us, Yamashita-sensei.
Let's count down to 321.
I didn't know that's what you meant... but she's cute... but beautiful... and scary... but...
She's scary as hell, like Ms. Kamaike.
No, she's beautiful.
So, Shirayama Shita gets Box 2. Congratulations on your graduation.
Bye!
Have them put the sea urchins in the fridge. So this is how the show will be recorded.
You'll be joining us now.
Why do I have to be embarrassed?
It's like the actress is getting a little too much light.
Next, the three rewards Umezawa wants. Next, the three rewards Umezawa wants.
Ta-da! Candy!
It's a candy bar!
After all, everyone gets really excited.
And the two bananaman guys like them too!
So if possible, I'd like them to be available all the time.
That's enough to make me happy.
Umezawa says that he would leave comments that make Bananaman laugh on the set for the sake of the candy.
I get rather nervous just by saying something.
So I thought I'd do my best.
So you mean you want to leave your mark on the recording.
That's right.
If you leave candy in the dressing room, everyone will try to leave their mark.
Today, we'll announce the seats with candy and the seats without.
That's what's scary.
Yamashita's scary, isn't he?
It's hard to make a mark.
What are you talking like a normal person?
You left your mark.
And as a second-hand reward, I bought some fruit with detonation in it.
Wooden box type.
So Inoue, you should've put something in a wooden box, like one piece or something.
Or a wooden box.
It's got to look like this.
What the hell is this?
If you give me this, I'll play a penalty game.
Punishment game?
Anything is OK.
Umezawa's prize is...
The Nimura Prize, which I definitely want!
Didn't we used to have the Himura Award?
If you win, Mr. Himura buys it for you.
That's right.
I just want to go on location with Bananaman.
I'm glad you said that.
We could go to an electronics store, or a picnic.
Wait a minute, I'm the one who's involved in that.
The Nimura Award for home appliances is really cool. The Nimura Award for Home Appliances is a real gimmick.
Don't call it an appliance store.
But you haven't been out on location much lately, have you?
No, we haven't.
That's why we're happy.
And I think we'll get to know each other better.
You guys are getting along great.
I'll have to buy him a few appliances.
For the Nimura Award.
I'll do whatever it takes to win the Nimura Award.
That's right.
So that's what this means.
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much Ume.
Thank you very much
I'm scared
Why this atmosphere?
It's so scary.
That was my last one, too.
That's for sure.
What's the reward for the youngest creek?
Here we go!
Delicious tomatoes!
I love tomatoes!
What are you doing with a good tomato?
Pie in the face.
They don't match.
It doesn't match.
Delicious warabimochi!
And the best reward for Ogawa's visit to the haunted house, which he hates, is...
Fine sushi!
Suddenly it's...
Suddenly it's real!
Suddenly something real!
What would you do if it was sushi?
I would fall into a pit! Then I'll fall into the pit.
Oh, no.
You know the pit's there, but you're still going for it.
That's a lot of food.
Yes, it is.
Tomatoes, sweets, sushi.
Food's dangerous.
Food is more likely to be here now.
Yes, it is.
That's for sure.
But how many tomatoes do you have?
I have tomatoes.
Tomatoes.
Why?
I have tomatoes.
Oh, my God.
What did I say?
Face pie.
Stand by for face pie.
Can you do it?
I'll take a tomato. You'll do it, right?
I'll take a tomato.
That's great.
You don't have to take this off yourself.
I'll get it for you.
Come on. Come on.
Let's go.
Okay, let's all countdown together.
Three.
Two.
One.
Here you go.
What?
LOL!
I didn't think I'd make it.
Here you go. Go ahead.
The pie in the face that happened to be there was not the beginning of the game.
So, one more shot.
OK.
Here we go.
Three.
Three... two... one.
One.
Here you go.
Ouch.
I know, I know, I know, I know, I know.
It's coming off, it's coming off, it's coming off.
Yes!
I'm in!
It's in!
You're the second person to paint white.
Oops, work over here.
Oh, what's this?
Oh, my God, they're working together.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
White on white!
And after his first pie in the face, Ogawa gets a delicious tomato
It's good, but there's a lot of cream in it.
Cream flavor?
It tastes like cream.
That was the end of the presentation.
Well, good job!
Ume and Yoda didn't do it?
No, they didn't.
Well, yeah.
To be honest, I wanted to do it.
I wanted to.
You can't do what you don't have, right?
There's no fruit in a wooden box.
I've got this.
Do you have it?
Why?
Why not? I'm gonna open it.
I'll open it.
It's there.
What? You got it?
There's a bad one.
Strawberries.
Strawberries!
They look so good!
Ume, what did you say about the crate?
Oh no!
It was a penalty game.
What did you say?
I'll do anything.
Oh, you do everything?
Do you have any extra bugs?
Extra bugs?
Open!
There it is!
You got any of these left over?
That's awesome!
This is the main course!
I really think this might be my first attempt at bugs.
Oh, no! There's some color on it.
You're seasoning it!
Oh, no! Oh, my stomach!
Oh, no, no, no!
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, my stomach!
Well, not all of them.
Oh, no!
I thought I really shouldn't eat bugs.
But you said I didn't have to do it.
That's right, it's just that this one's going away.
That's all!
Ugh, too bad!
But it's cool that you're doing this with this
It's cool.
It's cool. Cool.
Let's go tail anyway.
Let's just go for the tail.
Oh, my God!
One time.
Is it hard?
Oh, it's so hard!
It's so crunchy.
Oh, my God.
How's it taste?
It's delicious.
It's like iron beans.
Soybeans.
It tastes good.
The tail is like a bean.
I'm going to get one with a more squishy belly.
Oh, no!
I hope they go all the way to the middle anyway.
What's wrong, what's wrong, what's wrong?
What was that? What was that?
Soft tummy.
Soft belly.
Miso Denraku
That's good, that's good, that's good, that's good.
There it is! Next!
You're gonna eat all of it?
All of it?
We're going to eat it all.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Oh, my God.
I'm gonna eat it all.
Body gone, body gone.
I got the body, I got the body, I got the body.
I don't want a body.
Regal.
Regirl. Rigal.
What does "regirl" mean?
Regal.
What do you mean, "regirl"?
What is it?
Tell me.
What?
I'm on the Internet right now. It's all over the Internet right now.
Rigal.
Regal.
Oh, my God, that's great.
That's great.
It's not enough. Give me the Kimura award.
Oh, no.
Equal Opportunity Scoring Video to be determined.
Play Guide selection starts on the 12th.
Hello, I'm Aya Ogawa from Nogizaka 46.
I'm Aya Ogawa of Nogizaka 46. You just tried to close the screen, didn't you?
I'm going to sing a song now. Watch.
Here I go
I love me I love me I love me I love me
I love me I love me
I love me I love me I love me I love me I love me